Not every day is good
But there are some small beautiful things every day
Waiting for you
For example, now I share with you
Two very ordinary yet
delicious foods
One is the miso soup
that we Orientals love to eat
One is yogurt,
which is loved by Westerners.
Just like you
Even if you are born ordinary
Limited Edition
Don't give up
Ordinary you
Deserve better life
Hu Naiwen starts his lecture
I'm your old friend, Dr. Hu.
I want to share with you today
Miso fights cancer and relieves menopausal discomfort
Cooking miso soup this way brings you two great benefits
Yogurt plus it retains more good bacteria
Don't eat it with yogurt as it can cause cancer.
Miso bone care
Relieve menopausal discomfort
cold winter
Drink a bowl of hot miso soup
Life is short
If it tastes good, have another bowl.
Warms the stomach and body
I feel hungry
just talking about this.
Sure enough, handsome, humorous, kind and cute
Can't be eaten as a meal
What is miso made of?
Miso is made mainly from soybeans
with salt and different types of koji added for fermentation.
Become a fermented food
During the fermentation process
Convert the protein
into amino acids
Improve intestinal absorption
Miso has three health benefits
Protect bones, nourish the intestines, prevent cancer and fight aging
1. Protect bones
Miso contains plant protein
and three minerals: calcium, magnesium, and potassium
Maintains the structural strength of bones
When the body lacks calcium or magnesium
The bones will become
Loose and fragile
In addition to protecting bones
Miso also contains
soy isoflavones
Similar to female hormones
estrogen
is helpful for balancing hormones.
Dear girls
When you are now or in the future
Menopausal symptoms appear
Symptoms such as hot flashes, night sweats, and palpitations may occur
Have some miso tofu soup
Balance your hormones
It also
slows down your bone loss
Especially when you add tofu to miso soup
Did you know
Tofu also contains
High amounts of soy isoflavones
Plus the calcium content is relatively high
Paired with miso
Better nutritional effects
And it's really delicious
2. Nourish the intestines
The Aspergillus oryzae in miso.
It is a probiotic
Aspergillus oryzae helps
intestinal digestion and absorption
When cooking
Add a little miso
Make your intestines light
And smooth bowel movements
3. Anti-cancer and anti-aging
Miso is rich
in antioxidants
Effectively fight free radicals
Slow down cell aging
Let you radiate vitality
from the inside out
Did you know that the Japanese studied miso?
To what extent has the research been conducted?
A Japanese research report tracking
more than 90,000 people
It was found that people
who consumed more than 50 grams of miso per day
or soy products
Significantly reduced risk of death
Drink one to two bowls of miso soup daily
Helps reduce the incidence of breast cancer
and liver cancer
But why do some people say
that drinking more miso soup
increases the risk of cancer?
Actually, it’s because the miso soup
is too salty.
So when you drink miso soup
Can be diluted
Or choose products
with less salt
To avoid eating too salty
Damage to gastric mucosa
Increased risk of stomach cancer
Too much salt
may also damage your kidneys.
Cook miso soup last?
Add the miso soup last
Earn 2 major benefits
Moms, remember
Add miso last when cooking soup
Retain live bacteria to make the fragrance stronger
Over 45 degrees
The good bacteria in miso will be reduced
65 degrees
Heating for half an hour
can sterilize a large amount of
It will also boil away the aroma.
The method is very simple
Cook the soup
Mix the miso after turning off the heat
Smooth and sweet, full of rich mold aroma.
You are grilling fish and eggplant
Only apply miso when it's almost cooked.
Lock in nutrients and flavor
Next, we introduce the second fermented product.
yogurt
Eat yogurt twice a week
Reduce the risk of colorectal cancer and remove heat and toxins from the body
Yogurt
is known as longevity milk
Not only Westerners like
As early as before the Tang Dynasty
The ancients discovered its benefits
called lào(transliteration)
Modern yogurt
It is made from animal milk fermented
by lactic acid bacteria
Solid is called yogurt
Liquid is called yogurt
Even better
People with lactose intolerance
You can also eat it with confidence
Lactobacillus
breaks down lactose into lactic acid
Reduce gastrointestinal discomfort
sūn sī miǎo(transliteration), the King of Medicine in the Tang Dynasty
In the bèi jí qiānjīn fāng(transliteration), it is said
Lào néng bǔ fèi zàng lì dà cháng(transliteration)
This means that yogurt can not only nourish the lungs
but also promote large intestine peristalsis.
Compendium of Materia Medica also says
Lào rùn zào lì cháng néng bǔ xū sǔn(transliteration)
Strong physique
Yòng zhī zhì rè dú zhǐ kě xiāo tán rè(transliteration)
What this means is that
Yogurt not only nourishes the body
but also improves weakness
It can also resist heat toxins in the body
Such as abscesses, acne and other problems
Think about it
More than a thousand years ago
The ancients knew
This natural nourishing remedy
Is it super advanced?
Modern research also supports the benefits of yogurt
Mass General Brigham
Follow participants for 30 years
found that those who ate
more than two servings of yogurt per week
The risk of getting colon cancer
is lower.
It shows that regularly eating yogurt
not only helps regulate the intestines
but also can fight against some colorectal cancer
It's really good
Do you often suffer from constipation and indigestion?
or people with stomach blockage
Eat a cup of yogurt every day
to increase good intestinal bacteria
Inhibit bad bacteria and make the intestines healthier
Yogurt with it.
Retain good bacteria and upgrade nutrition
Flavored yogurt on the market
Or yogurt looks delicious
In fact
it may have added too much sugar and additives
Not only can you not enjoy the value of yogurt
It is also easy to gain weight
How to choose good yogurt
I recommend you eat this original yogurt
Select 4 key points
No gelatin, no sugar, no chemical additives.
Must also have live bacteria.
This will really help the intestines
Yogurt paired with some natural ingredients.
The effect is upgraded
Combination 1
Yogurt with honey
When you eat yogurt
You can add 1 tablespoon of honey
About 15cc
Honey can protect Bifidobacterium from being destroyed
and also provides minerals,
vitamins, and oligosaccharides
to help beneficial bacteria thrive.
It can also promote intestinal motility and improve constipation
Combination 2: Yogurt with Fruit
For example, berries like
Blueberry Cranberry Raspberry
Apples and peaches
These fruits contain mannitol
Mannitol
A natural prebiotic
Prebiotics are
food for probiotics.
Helps good bacteria in the intestines grow and thrive
Healthy bacteria are well-fed
resulting in a healthier and smoother intestinal environment.
Fruits rich in vitamin C
Together with the protein and calcium in yogurt.
Help regulate the intestines
Antioxidant and immune-enhancing
Combination 3: Yogurt and Walnuts
Walnuts are rich in Omega3
This is good fat.
Not only can
Protect cardiovascular health
It also helps
the brain function more flexibly
Three simple combinations
You can turn a small cup of yogurt into
A healthy product
with full nutrition
When is the best time to eat yogurt?
Don't eat it with it
Should yogurt be eaten before or after meals?
It is best to eat yogurt two hours after a meal
At this time, stomach acid is relatively low
Probiotics have a higher survival rate
And yogurt is colder
Eating after meals can avoid damaging the spleen and stomach
Some people also ask
whether yogurt can be eaten on an empty stomach?
No
Eating yogurt on an empty stomach
Probiotics are easily destroyed by stomach acid
It will also damage the spleen and stomach yang energy
What can't be eaten with yogurt?
Do not eat sausages, bacon, etc
immediately after eating yogurt.
High-fat processed foods
These processed foods
contain nitrite
Will be with the amine of yogurt
Form carcinogenic nitrosamines.
I don't recommend heating it.
Because the casein and whey protein in yogurt
It changes properties when exposed to heat
May cause
some nutrient loss
Cold weather
Don't want to eat ice yogurt
You can use this trick
Water-insulated heating
Heat water to about 40 degrees
Don't be too high
Under this temperature
The protein is relatively stable
But the probiotics will still die
If you want to keep probiotics
It is best to eat cold yogurt at room temperature
How much yogurt should you eat in a day?
It is recommended to consume 1 to 2 cups a day
200 to 250cc per cup
Provides approximately 8 to 15 grams of protein
Consume 2 to 3 or more cups per week
Long-term regular consumption is the best
Greek Yogurt Greek-Style Yogurt
The difference is in one place
There are two types on the market
Popular yogurt
Greek yogurt
Another type is called Greek-Styleyogurt
Many people think
that it is just a word difference.
Actually, the nutrition is very different.
The production methods are very different
Real Greek yogurt
According to traditional methods
Made from fermented whole milk
Filter the water
from the yogurt many times.
Concentrate both the milk and protein.
So the texture is very thick
The protein content is
higher than regular yogurt
Greek-Styleyogurt
The taste is also very sticky
But it is not made by repeatedly filtering whey.
Instead, add heavy cream or thickener
Like pectin, agar, gelatin, etc.
Simulate a thick taste
Although it looks very similar to Greek yogurt
But the protein content
is usually not as high as that of real Greek yogurt
Sometimes even higher in fat
So you want to eat
High-protein, pure and nutritious yogurt
choose
Greek yogurt is better
Dear fans,
We have opened the membership channel
If you agree with Dr. Hu's promotion of Chinese medicine
The concept of taking care of your own health
Small monthly donations are welcome
Or become a VIP sponsor
With you
We can go further
Thank you so much